<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MVC on Wouter Brunenberg</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mvc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MVC on Wouter Brunenberg</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>wouter.brunenberg@outlook.com (Wouter Brunenberg)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>wouter.brunenberg@outlook.com (Wouter Brunenberg)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mvc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beestje Op Je Feestje</title>
      <link>/portfolio/beestje-op-je-feestje/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>wouter.brunenberg@outlook.com (Wouter Brunenberg)</author>
      <guid>/portfolio/beestje-op-je-feestje/</guid>
      <description>Overview 🗺️ &amp;lsquo;Beestje Op Je Feestje&amp;rsquo; is an app we created in pairs using ASP.NET for a school project. The project mainly focused on validation rules, user authorization and authentication, unit testing, and hosting. An admin user can create animals with specific characteristics. These animals can then be rented by customers for a day, usually for parties. There are rules for choosing animals (for instance, some animals can&amp;rsquo;t be rented with certain others, based on their name or type).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temple of Doom</title>
      <link>/portfolio/temple-of-doom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>wouter.brunenberg@outlook.com (Wouter Brunenberg)</author>
      <guid>/portfolio/temple-of-doom/</guid>
      <description>Overview 🗺️ &amp;lsquo;Temple of Doom&amp;rsquo; is a console application developed using the .NET MVC framework. The goal of this assignment was to practice a lot of different design patterns. The front consisted of a console with different characters and colours, depending on the type of object and if it had a colour property assigned to it (in the case of a key or coloured door for example).&#xA;Technologies Used 🛠️ C# .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Bumbo</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-bumbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>wouter.brunenberg@outlook.com (Wouter Brunenberg)</author>
      <guid>/portfolio/project-bumbo/</guid>
      <description>Overview 🗺️ &amp;lsquo;Project Bumbo&amp;rsquo; was a group project I participated in during my school days, where our team of five was tasked with solving a pressing issue for &amp;lsquo;Bumbo&amp;rsquo;, a fictional supermarket chain. The challenge at hand was the time-consuming and inefficient scheduling process that the store manager faced every week. This often resulted in employees working overtime and shifts where the store was either understaffed or overstaffed.&#xA;Technologies Used 🛠️ C# ASP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Sagrada</title>
      <link>/portfolio/project-sagrada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>wouter.brunenberg@outlook.com (Wouter Brunenberg)</author>
      <guid>/portfolio/project-sagrada/</guid>
      <description>Overview 🗺️ &amp;lsquo;Project Sagrada&amp;rsquo; was a school project that marked my first significant collaboration, where I worked with a team of five to eight people (it increased because of issues in one of the other groups). This project introduced me to Git and GitHub. Our objective was to develop an online version of the board game &amp;ldquo;Sagrada&amp;rdquo; using JavaFX. We followed a detailed list of requirements to ensure the game was up to the standard.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
